# **Bui Chi Trung**

Location: Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Email: trungcspntl@gmail.com | Mobile: +84-0988864538 LinkedIn | GitHub | trungbc.com

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

I am a software engineer with over 2 years of experience. I have worked with various languages including **Go**, Python, PHP, and JavaScript. I have experience in managing large-scale projects and optimizing processes for parallel execution across multiple threads and nodes. My expertise extends to both REST and **gRPC** APIs.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **GPU Software Engineer**

#### Moreh

Ha Noi, Viet Nam | Dec 2023 - Present

- **Contribute to AMD's open-source library MIOpen**. MIOpen provides highly tuned implementations for standard operations in deep learning using AMD GPUs such as convolution, attention, matmul, etc.
- Parallelized AI model inference process using multiple threads, multiple GPUs, including GPUs distributed across different nodes, utilizing various techniques such as data parallelism and pipeline parallelism,...
- Project: Optimize an inference serving system with Llama-2 using multiple GPUs. Achieved throughput on 13 billion parameters model: **245 tokens/s**, equal to the state-of-the-art library for LLM inference <u>vLLM</u>.
- · Obtained skills: C++, CUDA, HIP

### **Backend Developer**

#### Teko VietNam

Ha Noi, Viet Nam | Aug 2022 - Dec 2023

- Fork <u>Superset</u>, an open-source platform for data exploration and visualization to customize authentication and authorization using Single Sign-On (SSO) flow. This enables seamless integration of Superset into Teko products.
- Develop and operate a service that stores data for over **50 million** users, capturing details such as transaction amounts and their most recent transactions, along with their online behavior including page views and interactions with commercial banners in **nearly real-time**. Leveraging this data, we automatically categorize customers and implement tailored marketing campaigns for each customer segment.
- Obtained skills: Go, gRPC, Microservices, Column-oriented database, React.

#### **DevOps Internship**

#### Worldquant

Ha Noi, Viet Nam | Apr 2022 - Jun 2022

Develop a service that controls google cloud platform instances used to execute quantive algorithms.

# **EDUCATION**

Banchelor. GPA - 3.84

**University of Engineer and Technology** 

Ha Noi, Viet Nam | Jul 2019 – Sep 2023

**English** : 900 TOEIC, 7.5 VSTEP

**Programming**: Fourth prize in Vietnam National Olympiad in Informatics - VNOI 2018

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages

: Golang | C++ | Java | Javascript | Python | PHP

Others

: MySQL | Redis | React. is | Vue | Laravel | Flask | gRPC | Docker | Git | Grafana

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Personal project

Golang, Redis, PostgreSQL.

Source Code

A custom plugin that can be integrated with Kong API Gateway to parse, build the Abstract Syntax Tree then cache GraphQL request routing through Kong API Gateway using Redis. Prometheus & Loki are integrated to manage the plugin state and log.

**Team project** 

Unitv. C#

Source Code

A Unity-powered Chinese chess game featuring 3D graphics, designed for immersive VR headset play. The game also includes support for voice commands and mouse control.